爸爸想让我们继承他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things. The family business.
攻击者是一名白人男子
Their attacker, a white male, 24 to 30 years of age.
- 这不是一幅好画面 - 变形人？
- Not a good picture. - Shapeshifter?
- 每一种文化里都有变形人的传说 - 它们可以变成任何东西
- Every culture has a shapeshifter. - Something that looks like anyone?
别动 趴下
Freeze. Stay on your knees.
- 他已经被怀疑是杀人凶手 - 杀人？
- He's been held on suspicion of murder. - Murder?
我们现在是在市中心的密尔沃基银行前
We're here downtown in front of the City Bank of Milwaukee…
在几分钟前这里发生了短暂的交火
and though a short exchange of gunfire occurred minutes ago…
在我们到达之前
police and SWAT teams maintain position…
警察和特警已经包围了三个小时
as we enter the third hour of this intense standoff.
专家估计仍有大约十名人质被困在银行里
Authorities estimate as many as 10 hostages are being held inside the bank.
到目前为止还没有关于嫌犯身份的消息
No word as yet on the identity of the suspects or-
- 有动静了 呆在原地 - 似乎有什么事发生了
- Coming out. Hold your position! - Something's happening.
我想他们正在开门 罗杰 你拍到了？
I think they're opening the door. Roger, are you getting this?
在那里 把镜头转到那边去
Hostage coming out. Stand down. Stand down. Hold fire.
别开枪 别开枪
Hey, don't shoot. Don't shoot. Please.
不 不 不 不 想都别想 都给我退后
No, no, no. Don't even think about it. Get the hell back.
别开枪
Please, don't shoot.
[邪恶力量 第2季第12集]
当FBI是种什么感觉？怎么说呢
So, what's it like, being an FBI guy?
这很危险
Well, it's dangerous.
是吗
Yeah.
我们需要保守秘密 很多秘密 数都数不过来
And the secrets we gotta keep. Oh, God, the secrets.
但最大的问题是 孤独
But mostly, it's lonely.
- 我完全同意 - 是吗
- I so know what you mean. - Yeah.
海琳娜是我们的老顾客了 她…
Helena was our head buyer. She…
她就象我们的家人 你知道吗？
She was family, you know? She said it herself.
每年圣诞节晚会上她都这么说 说我们是她唯一的亲人
Every Christmas party she said we were the only family she had.
所以没有任何迹象表明她会做那样的事
There were no signs that she'd do this?
没有… 直到现在我也不敢相信
No, I still can't believe it, even now.
那天晚上 海琳娜在关门后又回到这里
That night, Helena came back to the store after closing.
拿走了展柜还有保险箱里所有的珠宝
Cleaned out all the display cases and the safe.
正好被我们这儿值夜班的 安格儿发现了
Edgar, our night watchman, he caught her in the act.
他不知道该怎么办 他们认识了那么久
He didn't know what to do. He'd known her for years.
于是他给我打了个电话
He called me at home.
就是那时她抢走了他的枪？
And that's when she took his gun?
对着他的脑门就是一枪
She shot him in the face.
在电话里
I heard him die…
我听见他死了
over the phone.
那她的动机是什么呢？
Any idea what her motive could've been?
动机？这根本就很奇怪
What motive? It makes no sense.
为什么偷了所有的珠宝与钻石 仅仅是把它们藏起来？
Why steal all those diamonds, jewelry, then what, just dump it somewhere?
然后回家 接着
Just hide it and then go home and
她自杀了？
She killed herself?
警察说电吹风掉进了浴缸里 把自己电死了
The cops said she dropped a hairdryer in the bath and fried herself.
他们应该知道 是吧？
They should know, right?
对
Yeah.
好了 谢谢你 弗兰尼 我想这些就是我想要了解的
Well, thanks, Frannie. Think that's all I need.
真的？我的意思是 如果我知道的更多
Really? I mean, because I've got more.
你知道的 如果你还有问题想问我…
You know, if you wanted to interview me…
哪天 我们私下里谈谈？
sometime, in private?
可以 这真是个不错的注意
Yeah. Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
你真是个好公民 真的 为什么不把你的电话号码写在这儿给我？
You're a true patriot, you really are. Why don't you write your number down?
也就是说你自己从没看过监控录像
So you never saw the security camera footage yourself, then.
警察一来就把所有带子都带走了
The police, they took all the tapes, first thing.
他们当然带走了
Of course they did.
就是这了
Look at your file, this is it.
- 死警察 - 那是他们的工作
- Frigging cops. - They're just doing their job.
不 他们是在做我们的工作 他们不知道自己在干什么 弄得一团糟
No, they're doing our job. Only they don't know it, so they suck at it.
- 跟我说说那家银行 - 密尔沃基国家银行
- Talk to me about this bank. - Milwaukee National Trust.
- 大约一个月前曾被抢 - 和M。-O。-As珠宝店一样？
- It was hit a month ago. - Same M.O. as the jewelry store?
是的 一个干了很久的职员 「十年如一日」
Inside job, long-time employee. The never-in-a-million-years type.
那家伙抢劫了银行 然后回家 并按照推测同样自杀了
Dude robs the bank, then goes home and supposedly commits suicide.
- 罗斯尼克的工作是警卫？- 是的
Reznick was the guard on duty? Yeah.
- 事实上他被来抢劫的出纳员给打晕了 - 天哪
- He was beaten unconscious by the teller who heisted the place. - God.
是的
Yeah.
罗斯尼克先生
Mr. Reznick?
罗纳德·罗斯尼克
Ronald Reznick?
妈的
Son of a
我们是联邦调查局的 罗斯尼克先生
FBI, Mr. Reznick.
让我看下你们的证件
Let me see the badge.
我已经把我知道的都告诉警方了
Already gave my statement to the police.
听着 罗纳德 只是一些关于你的陈述的事情
Listen Ronald, just some things about your statement.
我只想从你的话中澄清一些事情
We want some clarification on it.
- 你们看过了？- 是的
- You read it? - Sure did.
- 要听听我的说法？- 这就是我们来这儿的原因
- Come to listen to what I gotta say? - That's why we're here.
好吧… 进来吧
Well, come on in.
自从我把真相告诉警察以后
None of the cops ever called me back.
他们就再没找过我
Not after I told them what was really going on.
他们都认为我疯了
They all thought I was crazy.
首先 胡安·莫拉瑞斯 没有抢劫密尔沃基国家银行
First off, Juan Morales never robbed the Milwaukee National Trust.
我可以保证
That I guarantee.
我和胡安是朋友
Me and Juan were friends.
他常在我值夜班的时候来找我 一起玩牌
He used to come back to the bank on my night shifts and we'd play cards.
所以那天晚上你让他进入了银行 在非营业时间
So you let him into the bank that night. After hours.
我让进入银行的…
The thing I let into the bank…
不是胡安
wasn't Juan.
我的意思是说 它和胡安长的一样 但是那却不是他本人
I mean it had his face, but it wasn't his face.
每个细节都那么完美 但太完美了 就像制作出来的一样
Every detail was perfect but too perfect.
就像我在和一个 胡安 的模型说话一样
Like if a doll maker made it, like, if I was talking to a big Juan doll.
- 一个胡安的模型？- 知道吗
- A "Juan doll"? - Look.
这种事不是第一次发生了 那次的珠宝店也发生过
This wasn't the only time. There was this jewelry store too.
警察和你们这些人… 你们只是没看见罢了
And the cops and you guys, I mean, you just won't see it.
两件案件都是被同一个东西干的
Both crimes were pulled by the same thing.
那么… 那个东西是什么 雷斯尼克先生？
And what's that, Mr. Reznick?
中国人已经研究好多年了 之前俄国人也研究过
Chinese been working on them and the Russians before that.
半人身半机械
Part man, part machine.
就像一样 但是这个却是能变形
Like the Terminator but the kind that can change itself.
变成看起来和其他人一样的东西
Make itself look like others.
- 就从前的T2 - 完全正确
- Like from T2. - Exactly.
所以并不仅仅是个机器人 更像是个… 类人机器人
See, not just a robot. More of a "mandroid."
一个类人机器人
A mandroid?
是什么让你如此肯定的 罗纳德？
What makes you so sure about this, Ronald?
我复制了所有的保安监视带
See, I made copies of all the security tapes.
我知道一旦到了警察手中 就拿不回来了 这儿
I knew once the cops got them they'd be buried. Here.
现在看这儿
Now watch.
快看
Watch.
看他 看 快看
Watch him, watch, watch.
看 就在那儿
See? Look, there it is.
看到了吗？他有一双激光眼
You see, he's got the laser eyes.
警察说那是某种光线反射
Cops said it was some kind of reflected light.
某种「红眼」 知道吗？
Some kind of "camera flare." Okay?
绝对不是该死的红眼
Aingt no damn camera flare.
他们说我个是精神创伤后的反应
They say I'm a post-trauma case.
然后呢？银行解雇了我 这没关系
So what? Bank goes and fires me? It don't matter.
可那个类人机器人还在逍遥法外
The mandroid is still out there.
如果法律不能将这东西绳之于法的话
The law won't hunt this thing down…
我会亲自动手
I'll do it myself.
知道吗 这个东西杀害了真正的人类 还伪装成自杀的现场
You see, this thing, it kills the real person. Makes it look like a suicide.
然后它就变形成那个人的样子
Then it, like, morphs into the person.
工作一段时间
Cases the job for a while till it knows the take is fat…
再找机会下手
then finds its opening.
这些抢劫案都发生在这附近
These robberies, they're grouped together. So I figure…
所以我认为那个类人机器人藏身在中间的某个地方
the mandroid is holed up in the middle.
也许是地下 我不知道
Underground maybe. I don't know.
也… 也许那是他给自己电池充电的地方
Maybe that's where it recharges its mandroid batteries.
好了
Okay.
我要你仔细听好了
I want you to listen very carefully.
因为我要告诉你这所有事情的真相
Because I'm about to tell you the gods' honest truth about all of this.
这并没有像类人机器人一样的东西
There's no such thing as mandroids.
也没有鬼怪或者非人类的东西 只是人
There's nothing evil or inhuman going on out there. Just people.
并没有别的 明白么？
Nothing else, you understand?
- 激光眼 那只是红眼 - 罗斯尼克先生
- The laser eyes. - Just a camera flare.
我知道你并不想相信这点
I know you don't wanna believe it.
但确实是你的朋友胡安抢劫了银行 就是这样
but your friend robbed the bank and that's it.
滚出我的房子
Get out of my house!
- 马上 - 没问题
- Now. - Sure.
不过得等我办完一件事
First things first.
老弟 你也太直接了吧
Man, that has got to be the kicker, straight up.
当你告诉那个可怜的家伙
You tell that poor son of a bitch that.
你怎么说的？要去收回他拷贝的带子
What did you say? Remand the tapes that he copied?
「进行中案件的机密证据」？简直胡说八道
Classified evidence of an ongoing investigation? That's messed up.
你干什么 生我的气了？
What, are you pissed at me?
我只是觉得你变成 这样好的一个联邦调查员感到很惊讶
I think it's creepy how good of a fed you are.
我们可以透露点消息给这家伙 他做了一些不错的前期工作
We could've thrown the guy a bone. He did some pretty good legwork.
- 「类人机器人」？- 除了类人机器人那部分
- Mandroid? - Except for the mandroid part.
我挺喜欢他 他与我们两个没有太多的不同
I liked him. He's not that different from us.
- 人们认为我们都是疯子 - 但他并不是个猎鬼者 迪恩
- People think we're crazy. - He's not a hunter.Dene
他只是一个意外发现了真相的普通人
He's a guy who stumbled onto something.
如果他去对付那家伙 他会被撕碎的
If he went up against this, he'd get torn apart.
不知道真相的话可能更好
Better to stay in the dark and stay alive.
恩 你说的对
Yeah, I guess.
变形者
Shapeshifter.
就像回到圣路易斯一样 在录象中同样的视网膜反射
Just like back at St. Louis. Same retinal reaction to video.
像相机的红眼现象
Eyes flare at the camera.
- 我恨这些该死的东西 - 你以为我不恨吗？
- I hate those frigging things. - You think I don't?
他又没变成你的样子杀人 陷害你
One didn't turn into you and frame you for murder.
如果这个变形者和我们在密苏里 杀掉那个一样的话
Look, if this shifter's anything like the one in Missouri.
那么罗纳德说的没错
Then Ronald's right.
好吧 他们喜欢在地下活动 下水道是个好选择
They like to lair up underground. Preferably the sewer.
之前所有的抢劫地点都是连在一起的 通过… 主下水道
All the robberies are connected so far to the sewer main layout.
在这个主下水道上还有一家银行
There's one more bank lined up on that sewer main.
我们的系统还没有发现任何问题
We haven't had any flags go up on our system yet.
不 只是整个系统的一个小故障
No, this is a glitch in the overall grid.
我们只是想保证银行的监控器没有问题
Just wanna make sure the branch monitors are kosher.
- 我想事后追悔不如事前稳妥 - 就是这个意思
- Better to be safe than sorry. - That's the plan.
到了 你们还需要其他帮忙吗？
Alrighty. You guys need anything else?
不 不 不 我们很快搞定 只是个例行检查
No, we'll be in and out before you know it. A routine check.
没有问题
Okey-dokey.
- 我喜欢他 他说「没有问题」 - 如果他是变形者呢？
- I like him. He says okey-dokey. - What if he's the shifter?
那样我们就跟踪他回家 然后用一颗银弹射穿他的胸腔
Then we follow him home and put a silver bullet through his chest plate.
好了 有爆米花吗？
Okay. Got any popcorn?
看起来是「没有问题」先生
Well, looks like Mr. Okey-dokey…
没有问题
is okey-dokey.
也许我们行动过早了 迪恩
Maybe we jumped the gun on this, Dean.
我们甚至都不知道他在不在这儿
We don't even know it's here.
也许我们就应该去下水道… 去… 去…
Maybe we should just go on back to the sewers and-
迪恩 我们应该寻找的是眼睛
We're supposed to be looking for eyes.
- 我正要看眼睛呢 - 是吗？
- I'm getting there. - Oh, yeah?
恩 等一下
Wait a minute.
- 你好 畸形人 - 找到他了
- Hello, freak. - Got him.
萨姆
Sam.
干嘛？
What?
你好啊 罗纳德
Hello, Ronald.
这不是抢劫
This is not a robbery.
所有人现在都给我趴在地上
Everybody on the floor now.
趴下 该死的
Get down, damn it.
快点 趴在地上 趴在地上
Come on, on the floor, on the floor.
到中间去
In the middle.
趴到中间的地上 到中间去 趴在地上 快点
On the floor in the middle. In the middle, on the floor. Come on.
动作快点 快
Hurry up. Come on.
你说我们不应该带枪
And you said we shouldn't bring guns.
我不知道会发生这事 迪恩
I didn't know this was gonna happen.
我去找他谈谈 我认为他不喜欢你 约翰逊联邦调查员
I'll do the talking. I don't think he likes you.
这里只有一条进出的通道 我把它用链子栓住了
Now there's only one way in or out of here and I chained it up.
所以没有人可以离开 明白吗？
So nobody's leaving, you understand?
嗨 伙计
Hey, buddy.
为什么不冷静下来 冷静下来
Now, why don't you calm down? Just calm down.
什么？
What the?
是你
You.
- 趴在地上 马上 - 好的 我们照做
- Get on the floor now. - Okay, we're doing that.
只是别杀任何人 特别是我们
Just don't shoot anybody. Especially us.
我就知道 你们俩一走我就知道 你们不是联邦调查员 你们是谁？
I knew it. As soon as you two left. You aingt FBI. Who are you?
你们为谁工作？你们是？
Who are you working for? The Men in Black?
- 你们为类人机器人工作？- 我们不是
- You working for the mandroid? - We're not.
你给我闭嘴 我没问你 我不喜欢你
You shut up! I aingt talking to you, I don't like you!
好吧
Fair enough.
到那边去 搜搜他们 看他们有没有武器 去啊
Get over there, frisk them down, make sure they got no weapons. Go.
看看我们找到了什么？
Now what have we here?
我不会什么都不带就来干活
I'm not gonna walk in here naked.
拿过来
Get back down.
别 别 别 别
No, no, no, no!
我们知道你不想伤害任何人 但是如果你一直晃那把枪就难说了
You don't wanna hurt anybody, but it will happen if you keep waving that.
- 你为什么不放这些人走呢？- 不 我已经告诉你了
- Why don't you let these people go? - No! I told you…
如果没有人来制止这那个东西 我就会亲自动手
if nobody's gonna stop this thing, then I gotta do it myself.
- 我们相信你 所以我们才会到这儿来 - 你并不相信我
- We believe you. That's why we're here. - You don't believe me.
没有人相信我
Nobody believes me.
怎么可能会相信？
How could they?
到这儿来
Come here.
什么？不
What? No.
你拿着枪呢 老大
You got the gun, boss,
你可以随时开枪 我只是想告诉你一些事情 到这儿来
you're calling the shots. I wanna tell you something.Come here.
是银行经理
It's the bank manager.
什么？
What?
你觉得我们为什么会装成这样
Why do you think we got these getups?
我们一直都在后面监视着银行 我们看到银行经理了
We were monitoring the cameras. We saw the manager.
我们看到了他的眼睛
We saw his eyes.
- 他的激光眼？- 是的
- His laser eyes? - Yes.
不 不 我们没有时间了
No.No. We're running out of time.
我们一定要在他变成其他人的样子前找到他
We gotta find him before he changes.
好象我会相信你一样 你是个可恶的骗子
Like I'm gonna listen to you. You're a damn liar.
我会开枪的 趴下
I'll shoot you. Get down!
抓我 抓我当你的人质 但是我们必须快点行动
Take me, take me with you as a hostage. But we gotta act fast.
因为我们在这浪费的时间越长 他就有越多的时间去变形
The longer we sit here, the more time he has to change.
看着我 伙计
Look at me, man.
我相信你
I believe you.
你不是个疯子
You're not crazy.
这家银行里面的确有些东西
There really is something inside this bank.
好吧
All right.
你… 你和我一起来
You come with me.
其他所有人都到保险库去
But everyone else gets in the vault!
快点 走
Come on. Move, move.
走 走
Come on, move.
然后你把它锁上
Move, move. And you lock it up.
没事的 大家… 尽量保持冷静
It's okay, everyone. Just stay cool.
旋转把手 旋转那的把手
Spin that. Spin that door.
那个男人是谁？
Who is that man?
他是我的哥哥
He's my brother.
他真勇敢
He is so brave.
检查桌子后面
Check behind the desk.
见鬼的这是什么？
What the hell is that?
好极了
Oh, great.
当他变形的时候 他会脱掉旧皮 所以 现在它可能是任何一个人
When it changes form, it sheds its old skin, so now it could be anybody.
太…
It's so…
太奇异了
It's so weird.
- 它的机器皮肤太像真的了 - 好了 我们现在实话实说
- Its robot skin is so lifelike. - Let's get something straight.
它不是个类人机器人
It's not a mandroid.
- 它是个变形者 - 变形者？
- It's a Shapeshifter. Yeah. - Shapeshifter?
是的
Yeah.
它是人类 多多少少
It's human, more or less.
它有人类的某些特性 在这情况下 是钱
Has human drives. In this case, it's money.
它培育自己的皮肤 他可以把皮肤变形成其他人的样子
But it generates its own skin. Shape it to match someone else's features.
- 所以它… - 它杀某些人然后取代那些人的位置
- Tall or short, male…It kills someone and takes their place?
- 杀人 我看倒没这必要 - 你在做什么？
- Kills or doesn't, I don't think it matters. - What are you doing?
不错
Nice.
你记得狼人的传说吗？和那些家伙很像
Remember the old werewolf stories? Pretty much came from these guys.
银制物品是唯一可以制服它们的东西
Silver is the only thing I've seen that hurts them.
跟我来
Come on.
快点 快点 我们走 离开这
Come on, come on, let's move. Move out of here.
好吧 快点 加快速度 速度 速度
All right, come on, let's hustle, hustle, hustle.
- 怎么样了？- 和以往差不多
- How we doing? - Another day in paradise.
- 还没有人出来？- 这家伙把自己锁里面了
- No one's come out yet? - This guy locked himself in.
他进去做的第一件事
The first thing he did.
好吧 切断电力
All right. Cut the power.
- 你疯了？- 正是如此
- Are you nuts? - That's just it.
我不是疯子
I'm not nuts.
我的意思是 我很怕丢了小命 但这居然是真的
I mean, I was so scared that I was losing my marbles. But this is real.
我想说 我是对的 除了变形人这点
I mean, I was right. Except for the mandroid thing. Thank you.
谢谢 不要放在心上
Yeah, don't mention it.
可恶 不 不 不 不 不
Damn it. No, no, no.
怎么了？
What? What is it?
他们切断了电力 大概这是他们跟我们说「你好」的方式
They cut the power. It's their way of saying hi.
- 谁？- 警察
- Who? - Cops.
警察？
The cops?
作为罪犯你还真是缺乏经验 罗纳德
You weren't exactly a smooth criminal about this.
你甚至连警卫都没看管 他大概通知了警方
You didn't secure the security guard, He probably called them.
- 我没想到 - 等等 让我们先稳定一下情绪
- I didn't think to-Hang on. Let's breathe, all right?
他们也许把我们包围了
They probably got us surrounded.
他们切断了摄像头的电力 所以现在没有办法告诉我们谁才是变形人
They cut the power to the cameras. No way of telling who the Shapeshifter is.
看上去不怎么好 罗纳德
It's not looking good, Ron.
听见了吗？
Did you hear that?
你兄弟是不是总是那么…
Has your brother always been so…
伟大？
wonderful?
我是说 骗开那把枪
I mean, staring down that gun.
然后摸透了那个变态家伙的想法
And the way he played into that psycho's crazy head…
说些他爱听的？
telling him what he wanted to hear?
- 他简直就是个英雄 - 是的
- He's like a real hero or something. - Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
- 你救了我们 你救了我们 - 事实上是我发现了一些东西
- You saved us. You saved us. - I just found a few more.
跟我来 伙计们 跟我走
Come on, everybody, let's go. Let's go.
- 你在做什么？- 萨姆
- What are you doing? - Sam?
我和 罗纳德 要和你谈谈
Ronald and I need to talk to you.
它又蜕皮了 不知道什么时候 可能在大厅或是进地下室的时候
It shed its skin again. We don't know. Could be in the halls, the vault.
不错
Great.
- 知道吗 迪恩 你正被警方通缉 - 是的
- Dean, you are wanted by the police. - Yeah.
即使我们找到那可恶的东西 我们怎么才能从这该死的地方逃出去？
Even if we do find this damn thing, how are we gonna get out of here?
现在的问题是
One problem at a time.
我要监视这里所有的地方 看看能不能找到异类
I'm gonna do a sweep of the place, find any stragglers.
之后把大家都聚在一起 就可以玩「找怪物」的游戏了
Once we got everybody, we play a game of Find the Freaks.
看这里 我找到了另一把给你
So here. I found another one of these for you.
你呆在这里 确保 罗纳德不会伤害任何人
Stay here, make sure Ronald doesn't hurt anybody.
- 看着他… - 看着他？
- Help him manage the situation. - Help him manage?
你发神经病吗？
Are you insane?
- 我知道这不是我们喜欢的方式 - 这叫什么
- This isn't going the way we wanted. - Understatement!
但是一旦警察进来 罗纳德和我们被逮捕
But if we let the cops in now, Ronald gets arrested, we get arrested.
变形人就会跑了
The shifter gets away.
可能再也找不到他了 好吧
Probably never find it again, okay?
罗纳德
Ron.
别暴露在光亮下
Out of the light.
- 你不会来真的吧？- 罗纳德的计划是个白痴计划
- Seriously? - Ron's game plan was a bad plan.
只不过有一点疯狂 但现在 是这城市的疯狂 明白吗？
It's a little bit of a crazy plan. But right now crazy is the only game in town.
你好 罗纳德
Hi, Ronald.
我让这开着 给你们些新鲜空气好吗？
I'm gonna keep this open, get you some fresh air in there.
但没人可以离开这里
But no one leaves this vault.
我不明白 你们为什么要帮他
I don't understand. Why are you helping him?
我告诉你 你也不会相信的
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
你好？我想我不得不离开这里
- Hello? - I think I gotta get out of here.
- 先生 我非常抱歉 你还是得待在这里 - 什么？
- Sir, I'm sorry but you gotta stay put. What?
- 你什么意思？条件？- 罗纳德…
- What do you mean, demands? - Ron.
- 挂上电话 - 我不是抢匪
- Hang up. - I'm not a bank robber.
- 我真的要离开这里 - 先生 你不能走
- I gotta get out of here. - You can't leave.
我猜是打击罪恶
I'm kind of a crime fighter.
- 亨利 深呼吸 好吗？- 罗纳德
Henry, just breathe, okay? - Ronald!
- 听着 - 不 我一个人
- Look-No, I'm acting alone.
罗纳德…
Ronald?
- 警察知道的越少越好 - 我想这位老兄的心脏病发了
- The less the cops know, the better. - This dude's having a heart attack.
好吧 要么是我们的人 要么是骗子
Great. Could be our guy, could be a trick.
- 你想让他死？- 没有人会死在这里
- Are you just gonna let the man die? - No one's dying here.
看着门
Cover the door.
能不能告诉我有多少人质被劫持？
Can you tell me how many hostages?
我们这里有人心脏病复发了 你们得派个急救人员来
One could be having heart trouble. You need to send in a paramedic.
- 保持冷静 我让你们出来 - 进来个急救人员 好吗
- Just stay calm, we'll have you out…Send in a paramedic.okye
不要耍花招 听见了吧
Don't try anything else. Please.
急救人员？他已经没有时间等了
Paramedic? Guy don't have time.
听着 我很抱歉 但是没有人可以离开这里
Listen, I'm sorry. Okay? I am. But nobody's getting out.
他会死在你的面前
He's dying right in front of you.
救救我
Help.
来吧 伙计 你可以打开前门
Come on, man. You gotta unlock the front door.
我们可以让他走
We've gotta get him out of here.
都站在那里别动
Both of you, stay where you are.
你明白什么 罗纳德？
You know, Ronald…
他是对的 我们让他出去 快点
he's right. We gotta get this man outside. Come on.
我扶你 我来帮你
Yeah, I'll help you.
哦 我来就行 真好
Oh, I got him. It's cool.
- 多谢 - 谢谢你
- Thanks. Thank you.
- 小心脚下 - 谢谢 谢谢
Watch your step. Sure. - Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 我能和你谈谈吗？
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
现在你说了算
You got the gun, man.
什么都行
Whatever.
停下 快回来
Stop, come back here.
趴下 罗纳德
Get down, Ron!
所有单位注意 我们有5到12名人质…
All units be advised, we have five to 12 hostages…
在城市银行的密尔布拉德利中心
in the City Bank of Milwaukee Bradley Center.
好 走 走 走
Yes, go. Go, go.
拿着
Here.
小心狙击手 我去追变形者
Take care of the guard. I'm going after the shifter.
对不起 小罗
Sorry, Ron.
你干的很好 非常棒
You did a real good job tracking this thing. You really did.
- 上帝啊 请别伤害我们 - 你们这个时候不应该到这儿来
- Oh! Please don't hurt us. - You shouldn't be back here.
这里很危险 回到保险库里去 现在就去
You're in danger. Now go back to the vault. Now.
人质在银行中心…
Hostages in the City Bank…
很快就好了
This will all be over soon.
等候通知
Stand by for further.
- 你会没事的 - 别开枪 别开枪
- Everything's gonna be all right. - Hey, don't shoot. Don't shoot, please.
不 不 不 不 退后
No, no, no. Back up.
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
求你了 别开枪
Please don't shoot.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
我说了 马上退后
I said, get back, now!
原来的人质之一现在掌控局势
One of the hostages, he seems to have taken over the situation.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
走 走
Okay. Go, go.
走
Get down.
这下搞砸了
We are so screwed.
- 喂？- 他又脱皮了
- Yeah? - He's slipped his skin.
- 什么？- 是的 这混蛋变形的很快
- What? - Yeah, bastard shifts fast.
比圣路易斯那个快多了
Faster than the one in St. Louis.
他喜欢玩蒙面游戏 它又有可能是任何一个人了
It's like playing a shell game. Could be anybody again.
- 我想大多数的职员都在保险库里 - 你仔细搜索这每一个角落
- The employees are out of the vault. - You search every inch.
我去把大家都集中起来
I'll round everybody up.
- 该死 - 怎么了？
- Crap. - What?
联邦调查局的人来了
The feds are here.
哦… 真该死
Oh, crap.
- 罗巴斯中尉 - 是的
- Lieutenant Robards. - Yeah.
特别调查员 汉迪克森
Special Agent Henriksen.
让我猜猜 下一句是我来接管 但还要求我们全力配合
Let me guess. You're lead dog now, but you'd just love my full cooperation.
我他妈的不管你做什么 你可以去买个甜圈吃或者回你老婆的被窝里
I don't give a rat's ass what you do. Get a doughnut and bang your wife.
我需要的是你的特别行动小组全副武装待命
What I do need is your SWAT team, locked and loaded.
听着 特别调查员 这个案件有些不对头
Listen, agent, something's not right about this.
这…
It's
- 这并不像一个普通的抢劫案 - 那是因为这根本就不是
- It's not going down like a usual heist. - That's because it isn't one.
你根本就不知道你在跟谁打交道 是吧？
You have no idea what you're dealing with, do you?
那个银行里面有一个怪物 罗巴斯
There's a monster in that bank, Robards.
我以为你是一个好人
And I thought you were one of the good guys.
- 你叫什么名字？- 你为什么关心这个？
- What's your name? - Why would you care?
我叫 迪恩
My name is Dean.
我是 雪莉
I'm Sherri.
嗨 雪莉
Hi, Sherri.
一切都会好起来的 这所有的一切很快就会结束的 好吗？
Everything's gonna be all right. This will all be over soon, okay?
- 哪位？- 我是特别调查员 威克特 汉迪克森
- Yeah. - This is Special Agent Victor Henriksen.
我现在没有谈判的心情
Yeah, listen, I'm not in the negotiating mood.
好的 我也没有 我本来是想让你活着走出来
Me neither. It's my job to bring you in.
活着的惊喜 现在看来没必要了
Alive's a bonus, but not necessary.
这话从联邦调查员嘴里说出来真荒唐 你不这么认为吗？
Kind of harsh for a fed, don't you think?
你并不是普通的罪犯 对吗 迪恩？
You're not the typical suspect, are you, Dean?
我要你和萨姆放下武器出来
I want you and Sam out here, unarmed.
否则我们就进去 是的 我知道萨姆 你的古怪兄弟
Or we come in. And yes, I know about Sam too. Bonnie to your Clyde.
是的 部分正确 但是你们怎么会知道我们在这儿的？
Well, that part's true. But how'd you know we were here?
自己好好想想 那才是原因
Go screw yourself. That's how.
了解你已经成为我的工作了 迪恩 我已经找你好几个星期了
It's become my job to know about you. I've been looking for you for weeks.
我知道圣路易斯的谋杀案 也知道你在巴尔的摩耍的戏法
I know about the murder in St. Louis, the Houdini act in Baltimore.
我知道你妖鬼神灵欺骗人的谎言 我还知道你的父亲
I know about the desecrations, the thefts. I know about your dad.
- 你根本不知道我父亲 - 退役海军 他在路上的孩子们
- You don't know crap about my dad. - Ex-Marine, raised his kids on the road.
廉价旅馆 偏僻的木屋 典型的准军事活命至上主义者
Cheap motels, backwoods cabins. Real paramilitary survivalist type.
我只是搞不清楚他到底是什么类型的疯子
I just can't get a handle on what type of wacko he was.
隐居者 晶片植入人 同性恋 变态
White supremacist, Timmy McVeigh, tomato, tomato.
你没有权利那样说我的父亲
You got no right talking about my dad like that.
- 他是个英雄 - 是的 听起来很像
- He was a hero. - Yeah. Right. Sure sounds like it.
你有一个小时做决定 不然我们就直接冲进去
You have one hour to make a decision or we come, full automatic.
召集你的人 5分钟后 我们进去
Scramble your men. Five minutes, then we go in.
什么？汉迪克森 他们目前为止已经放了一个人质
What? Henriksen, they've let out one hostage so far.
- 就目前来看他们没有伤害任何人 - 你不了解温彻斯特家的人
- They've hurt no one. - You don't know these Winchesters.
- 他们很危险而且受过特殊训练 - 我们不能拿里面人的生命做赌注
- They're dangerous and expertly trained. - We can't risk all those people.
- 相信我 迪恩相对于我们的行动更为危险 - 这太疯狂了
- Trust me. Dean's a risk to them. - This is crazy.
疯狂的行为在里面 我们只是去阻止
Crazy's in there and I just hung up on it.
该死
Damn it.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我们外面有点麻烦
We got a bit of a problem outside.
我们的麻烦在这里
We got a problem in here.
雪莉？我们要放你走
Sherri? We're gonna let you go.
什么？
What?
- 为什么是我？- 对联邦调查员表示友好 来吧
- Why me? - As a show of good faith to the feds.
我想我最好和其它人一起呆在这儿
I think I'd rather stay here with the others.
我想我会坚持我的想法
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to insist.
我以为你是要放我走
I thought you were letting me go.
你是个业余演员 还是天生是块演戏的料？
Is that community theater or are you naturally like this?
这是你最后一次装成别人 最后一次
This is the last time you become anybody. Ever.
哦 上帝啊
No. Oh, God. Oh…
迪恩 等等 等等 等等
Dean, wait.wait.wait.
她这样做有什么好处？
What's the advantage of this plan?
我的意思是说 现在晕倒并不会帮它逃掉
I mean, fainting now wouldn't help it survive.
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
把她从这儿弄出去 马上去
Get her out of here. Now!
别开枪 别开枪
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
我在这儿工作 我在这儿工作
I work here. I work here.
把我从
Please get me out.
这带出去
Please get me out of here.
别动
Freeze!
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hands.
恶心…
Gross.
行动 安全
Clear in here. Clear. Move.
安全 安全 走
Clear. Clear. Go.
前进
Clear. Move.
安全
男性 非洲籍美国人 没救了
Male, African-American. Goner.
告诉你 伙计 我刚刚把他送到银行外了
I'm telling you, man. I just walked her out of the bank.
她肯定是有个双胞胎姐妹或者什么的
She must have a twin sister or something.
长官 我的小组报告说这里已经安全了 他们逃掉了
Sir, my team said it's secure. They're gone.
你告诉你的小组把这给我翻个底朝天
You tell your team to tear it apart.
- 管道 棚顶 所有的地方 - 我认为没那必要了
- Ducts, ceiling, furnace, everything. - That's not necessary.
为什么？
Why not?
我们真的搞砸了
We are so screwed.